One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Adventure on the Ghost Island and
the Famous Doctor Hogback!
What is a ghost island, anyway?
Hey...
Hey, where did that ghost from earlier go?
Is it still onboard?
No, it floated towards that island.
It probably lives there.
Earlier there was a lot of shaking...
Perhaps it was the sound from that mouth-like gate closing?
I think we were "eaten" by that mouth.
Eaten?
It is difficult to tell with all this fog,
But it looks as if there's a fence that extends from the gate all the way around the island.
Which means that we have been trapped inside that fence.
Current Location
"Mouth" Gate
Ghost Island
"Thriller Bark"
Oh yeah!
That must be why that skeleton told us to hurry and get out of here!
That would mean that somebody made this into a wandering island!
But why?
Whatever the reason, what matters is that we are in the middle of the ocean.
We can not drop anchor here.
Hey hey, why are you talking about stopping?!
We need to leave now, before we're cursed!
Listen, everyone...
I think I have the "I can not go on that island" disease.
Me too!
I have that too!
Alright!
Then you guys can stay here!
You have "all ready for adventure" disease?!
Reconsider it!
Luffy, take a good look!
That creepy building over there...
That is a real haunted house!
You're underestimating...
Evil spirits.
What're you talking about?
I am gonna be as careful as I can!
I will catch that ghost from before and keep it as a pet!
Way underestimating!
But anyway, we have got to get back
our precious crewmate.
Sanji, pirate lunch box!
Crewmate?
I am against that!
If you let that skeleton come with us, I will be too scared to sleep at night!
I have the lunch.
Luffy, Franky.
You two take good care of Robin-chan.
Going to explore an unknown island just gives me the chills.
You're kidding me!
Robin's going too?!
I love thrills.
Alright!
Alright you guys, we're gonna have to take a boat out to the island.
But you guys still haven't seen my present.
Soldier Dock System Channel Two.
Two?
This system has five channels.
There are two zeros, and then,
One,
Two,
Three,
Four.
Each one has its own specialized use.
Hold on.
We've already seen Zero's paddles, along with Docks One and Three.
But you said Two and Four were empty!
I told you that 'cuz it's a present!
The guys who aren't going to the island can test it out first.
Soldier Dock System Channel Two!
Here it is!
What is it?
What is going to come out?
The steam-powered...
Paddleship!
The shopping boat,
Mini Merry #2!
It is Merry!
Merry came back to us!
It's kinda small, but now we can ride Merry again!
I can't believe he had such a great present...
Thank you, Franky!
If that's our shopping boat, I'd go shopping any time!
It's my turn! Hurry up, it's my turn!
That's really great.
Just hold on Straw Hat,
We'll ride it here soon.
Let them have fun with it for now.
Is that all of them, Franky?
Yeah.
Combined with One and Three, which you saw earlier, this is all of 'em!
Channel Zero - Support Paddle!
Channel One, a waver that can hold one person - White Wooden Horse #1!
Channel Two, a shopping boat that can hold four people - Mini Merry #2!
Channel Three, a scouting submarine that can hold three people - Shark Submerge #3!
Right now, that is the whole Soldier Dock System.
Just think of them as soldiers helping out Thousand Sunny.
I really like the way you think, Franky!
You! You! You!
Yeah, I am just really great this week too...
Super!
Nami-san!
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
What're they up to?
I can't see anything with this fog.
It came from the direction of the island.
You guys!
Hurry and let me ride on Mini Merry too!
Bastard, you need to worry about Nami-san's safety!
And you need to worry about the other two's safety too.
Perhaps she screamed as she was cursed by a ghost?
Stop that, it's not funny.
What?
Nobody was touching the anchor...
It's still brand new, so the gears shouldn't be that worn out yet...
Hurry and bring it up, the ship's gonna overbalance!
What?
Did someone do that?
No.
Nobody's close enough.
Luffy!
What are you doing?
Stop screwing around at a time like this!
Nyo, yats not ish!
No, that's not it!
Yaim noi joing anyjing!
I'm not doing anything!
Look out, Straw Hat!
Hey, bastard!
What the hell was that for?!
Sorry, my sword just did that...
This is weird...
With the exception of us... on this deck...
There's something else.
Maybe a ghost did it?
Or a devil fruit user, or somethin' like that?
Yeah, it felt like someone was grabbing me.
I heard the growl of a wild beast.
A beast?
Anyway, I'm worried about Nami-san!
You guys take care of the ship!
I'm gonna go save those guys!
So uncool!
Woah, Sanji's floating!
How is that possible?!
You made a "hogeh"-noise.
Shut up, you!
You would've done the same!
We can't even leave the ship?
What are they trying to do?
If they wanted us dead, they could've done that by now...
What's wrong, Robin-chan?
Something's... grabbing me...
How dare you do something like that!
Robin-chan!
There really is an animal!
What now?
Look!
A wave!
It has gotta be some sort of artificial one to be inside this fence!
The ship's gonna capsize!
Robin-chan, is it gone?
I'm fine, I think it left.
Hey, Hogeh, raise the anchor, or we're gonna sink!
Who the hell is "Hogeh"?!
Usopp! Chopper!
Can you hear us?
Damn, we're gonna be seperated from Nami-san.
Hey Franky!
Do something with the secret weapon!
Alright, I've got the "Flying Surprise Pool" we can use!
That sounds fun!
You idiot!
O-Ouch!
Of course you're hurt.
We must've fallen down here.
Where are we?
We're on the ghost island.
Ghost!
Oh, stop that!
You don't need to be scared!
But just what happened to us?
We were having so much fun on Mini Merry that we accidentally hit the bank.
We were distracted and couldn't see in the fog...
All three of us were sent flying...
And in the blink of an eye, we were here.
It's 100% my fault, but...
You'll forgive me since I'm cute, right?
I'll get you for this!
I'm very sorry.
But anyway, it's weird that just after getting to this island there's a huge ditch!
It's probably to catch their enemies.
We're just lucky it wasn't filled with spikes.
Yeah,
We're safe 'cuz we landed on these skeletons.
I told you to stop!
But this must be the entrance.
If we just wait here, Luffy will find us.
But we're lower than sea level, that's kinda scary.
Yeah, it's dangerous, and they might not be able to see us here.
So should we wait on the bank above?
The bank?
But I don't know which way...
What's that?
A dog?
That's not a dog...
Then... then what is it?
That... it can't be...
Ce... Ce...
Cerberus!
It's Cerberus!
W-What is Cerberus?
It's the guard dog of hell!
It really exists?!
It must, it's right behind us!
So this is hell?!
We're in hell!
Just keep running!
If it catches us, it'll eat us!
Hey, what is it, Chopper?
Chopper, what do you see?
"Kon"...?
Hey, look at it carefully!
Isn't one of them a fox?!
Now it's saying "gon"!
It really didn't like it!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Look, stairs!
We can leave that way!
Thank god!
Does it have a bad sense of smell, even though it's a dog?
It left...
What now?
We ended up in a forest...
If that thing's walking around, then if we're anywhere not hidden we're in danger...
You are correct, sir.
Who are you?!
I am known as Hildon.
I saw that you all were being chased by the guard dog,
So I followed you in secret, in case you had trouble.
It will be night soon, after all.
This forest will become incredibly dangerous to those like yourselves who are unfamiliar with it.
So if you wish, I can take you to our mansion.
Mansion?
Yes...
Doctor Hogback-sama's mansion.
What is it?
What's wrong, Chopper?
Hogback?
Hey...
I couldn't see the horses very well through the fog, but...
Is there something wrong with them?
Oh, it's only your imagination.
That... that's alright then...
Anyway, you saved us.
Thanks, we were in trouble.
Oh no, it's my pleasure.
Would you like a drink?
This forest is full of odd animals, so walking through it is dangerous.
Yeah, I was pretty surprised.
I thought Cerberus was just a made-up creature.
It looked like a mutant or something.
I was wondering if we'd ever be able to get down from that tree.
If you're waiting for others, the mansion is ideal.
It's very visible, and very safe.
And we'll also be able to meet Doctor Hogback.
Is he really that famous?
Every doctor's heard of him.
He's a surgical genius!
With his miraculous operations, he's saved countless numbers of people!
He has all the status and honor a doctor can get,
And he's respected by doctors everywhere!
But one day,
he suddenly disappeared.
There were rumors that he had been abducted,
and the doctors of the world were all in an uproar.
But after years went by without a trace,
Hogback's name is now simply a legend...
That Doctor Hogback?!
Yes, even now the Doctor is researching new things.
I hope I can get an autograph!
I'm sure we can arrange it.
No way...
There are even lions in this forest?
What was that for?!
Don't scare me like that!
What's wrong?
W-Well, just now, there was a l-lion...
Like this.
Yeah, right!
Then, take a look for yourself!
See?
Food, food, food!
Something's there!
Something's definitely there!
Wait up a sec!
Please stop the cart, Hildon-san!
Why are you so upset?
Perhaps you were just seeing things?
No, she wasn't!
There's something out there!
This forest is too weird!
Yes, it is a strange forest.
And, due to the thick fog and people's paranoia,
many people believe they see things out here.
So, it wasn't real?
That's good...
No, wait...
An illusion?
No, it was way too clear!
Hildon-san,
I'm sorry, but could you just bring us to the coast?
I know it's dangerous, but we can handle it.
But then I can't meet Doctor Hogback!
I wanna meet him!
No, no, I know how you feel.
But this time we gotta rely on our special ability, the "something's fishy here” sensor!
Would you die to meet that doctor...
Would you survive and not meet him so you can leave the island...
Which do you pick?
Well, I don't wanna die.
I'm too scared.
Oh, is that so?
If that is what you wish...
Everyone, please wait here.
Stop the cart!
Sorry for taking away your chance, Chopper...
It's okay, I'm just no good at running off and doing my own thing like Luffy does...
10 minutes later...
Silence...
That's weird, all he was doing was turning it...
There's nobody there!
The horses are gone too!
We're all alone in the middle of a graveyard!
What?!
How?
He abandoned us?
M-Maybe he just went to the bathroom!
Hildon!
Hey, where'd you go?
But why a graveyard, of all places?
What?
No... no way!
Zo...
Zombies!
Ow, ow!
Usopp!
They're gonna tip the cart!
These guys're really strong!
He bit me!
Dammit, he bit me!
Now I'm gonna turn into a zombie!
Usopp!
I'll save you!
No, don't!
Stop!
Save me!
Let Usopp go!
Bastard!
I'm sorry!
Hey, you dropped this.
Thanks.
Save me!
They're gonna bite me!
Nami!
Let go...
Stay back!
A zombie's weakness is...
Deadly...
Flame Star!
Fire!
Careful, you'll burn up!
It worked a lot better than I'd thought...
How dare you do that to us, bastard!
What would you've done if you'd hit us, idiot?!
You rotten person!
But now the zombies are really mad!
Let's go, Nami!
Let’s get away now!
Now that we're this far, it's closest to just run to the mansion!
Yeah, let's do that!
That was scary...
It's alright!
Once we get out of the graveyard, we'll be fine if we run as fast as we can!
All zombies can do is groan and walk really slowly!
Slowly, slowly!
Wait, you bastard!
They're fast!
I'm tired...
They have no stamina!
I think... we lost them...
What is wrong with this island?
It's just covered with things that shouldn't be alive...
Hey, guys...
If I turn into a zombie, then you can just-
What are you talking about?
I read it in a book on zombies I found in Sunny's library.
For being scared of these things, you sure read a lot about them.
Well, here we are.
I just want a glass of water.
I can finally meet him!
This is great!
I bet that on an island like this...
You can't find a single honest person living on it.
Excuse us!
Is this Mr. Doctor Hogback's mansion?